facing difficulties in your remote job
say hello to fluent boards a one-size
fits-all WordPress solution for you to
make remote project management a breeze
with smooth workflow easy client
management and improved team
collaboration work better together from
home fluent boards is made for WordPress
users the dashboard gives instant access
access to recently open boards and your
tasks whether working on a single
project or multiple you can create
unlimited boards for managing them all
break down your big goals into
manageable
tasks assign due
dates set priorities and add custom
label for each one detailed description
and attachments ensure everyone on your
team is on the same
page with easy resource access no more
or endless searching through emails or
cloud storage folders everything is
right on the spot to handle these tasks
you can add as many members as you need
no limitations at all and the invite
member option lets you onboard members
from outside WordPress
ecosystem once they are in assign tasks
to them or join yourself as an assig
otherwise turn on the watch and get
notified about each activity in the task
you can also use the cover for extra
visibility need more flexibility add sub
tasks with deadlines and assign your
team members or even convert it into a
task if needed Flint boards is more
about working smarter than harder make a
template reflects this very well create
a test template once and reuse it
anytime saving your precious
time managing clients remotely has never
been easy but fluent boards is here to
turn the tables for you just like with
your team members you can add or invite
clients directly to your project board
don't want to do that fluent board's
easy integration with fluent CRM has got
your back simply add your client CRM
contact to any task their details are
always at your fingertips you can even
create automation with ease to notify
your clients about each stage of your
project and flu board's integration with
fluin forms is well prepped to defend
you against project crepe create a form
map fields and attach it to your desired
project board clients can easily submit
their suggestions and those suggestions
will be automatically added to your
project board but trust me there's a lot
more to
uncover with top class client management
it becomes crucial to complete tasks on
time fln boards time tracking can be
handy in such instances set an estimated
time and then the assign can manually
log the time and description soon this
will be automated making the process
even smoother not just that you can
search for specific tasks or filter them
by assigning stages due date or priority
level tracking performance will never
pose an issue and the activity gives you
the details you need on any tasks you
want using these you can track
performance easily identify model NE and
keep projects moving forward at
lightning
speed monitoring workflow is equally
important as tracking performance for me
a personalized word view comes first Flo
boards lets you switch between combon
boards or detail list seamlessly you can
even personalize your card view
preferences to see your tasks your way
but that's just the tip of the iceberg
click these three dots and A Whole New
World of options opens up access board
activity change the background color
manage board labels view board members
duplicate or delete boards and much
more you know one of the biggest
challenges in remote project management
is staying in constant communication
what can be better than email for that
choose exactly when you want to be
notified and never miss an important
work update again got tasks to discuss
ideas to share or achievements to
celebrate the comment section is all
yours for team connection and
collaboration so no more feeling
isolated even when working remotely stay
connected stay
happy for remote project management
safeguarding sensitive project
information is Paramount FL boards lets
you manage member roles and permissions
to safeguard data effectively in case
you want to mind migrate from Trello or
Asana directly import data without
losing any of it easy and neat from
communication to information
safeguarding everything is sorted and
thanks to fluent boards for making it
happen whether working Solo or leading a
remote team the Herculean task of
project management becomes a child SP
with fluent boards so are you ready to
bid farewell to the hassle of remote
project management and start managing
projects with fluent board
don't forget to let us know